mightystudents.com 2010-08-25

# Privacy Policy

MightyStudents.com is committed to protecting your personal, contact and other information as well as your privacy. Our privacy statement was designed to make it clear why we collect certain information from you, to whom that information is disclosed, and how we protect your privacy. Information collectedBy submitting any of our online forms, you agree to the collection, processing and use of the information by MightyStudents.com. 

**How your information is used**  
Your information may be used in any one of the following ways: 

  * To provide you with an instant estimate of our services.
  * To monitor customer traffic and site usage to help us improve the design and general layout of the site.
  * To analyze your browsing preferences to help us select products or services that you may be interested in.

**Data Security**

  * We will not ask for unnecessary information, only information needed to process your subscription.
  * We do not store any information about you which is no longer relevant.
  * We protect your information against unauthorized use. We enforce highly secure procedures in the storage and disclosure of information to prevent unauthorized access.
  * We will never rent, sell or give away your email address or other information to anyone.

**Cookies**  
MightyStudents.com uses cookies to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content on your later visits to these sites. MightyStudents.com does not use cookies to track your movements around this website. 

**Information from credit cards**  
All the online transactions are processed through the secure and reliable online payment system provided by Authorize.net. It’s the safest and the most convenient way to send online payments with no risk of having your credit card data disclosed to any third party.  
All the transactions are handled by a secure server and discarded once the transaction is completed. 

**Changes to the present privacy statement**  
MightyStudents.com may amend the present privacy statement once in a while. Please visit regularly the current page to follow any changes in our privacy policy If you have any questions or comments about our privacy statement or practices, please contact us via email at [info AT mightystudents.com](mailto:info@mightystudents.com)

Testimonials

Thomas, Vancouver  
Your site is my one stop shop for all of my reference papers and I use it frequently. Your da... 

Antonio, Bologna, Italy  
I am from Italy and have problems writing in good English and do not know how to write the many kind... 

Read more
